when you f it up oh oh and if you f it
up cuz this is
[Music]
Africa all right guys so right now we
are in London the not so beautiful city
of London you guys can see the weather
uh not the best place we are leaving
right now and going to Africa for the
first time it's all of our first times
we just finished the London meet and
greet we're coming from Madrid we did a
meet and greet in mrid London now we're
going to Africa and after Africa we're
going to Dubai so we've been out already
for about a month we're fried we've been
on the road with 18 different luggages
for 3 weeks already we still got like
another 3 weeks to go so literally on
our way to the airport right now where
we got the 13-hour flight straight to
Africa one way no stop it about to be
brutal huh on our way to Africa to see
the Lions hoping they speak Spanish over
there this flight 20 grand you don't
know that right no not at all fuing 20
grand first class I me obviously have to
get a lay down 13 sorry all right we'll
be there one day I hate this part hate
this part can you just like all right
and now we're here so we actually pulled
up we were supposed to be in Africa but
there's a Gordon Ramsey in the first
class section when you flying out of
London so we're still here at the
airport I'm going a 24-hour fast this is
the only way how you should properly
break the fast pasta burger and some mac
and cheese thank you yeah yeah now I'm
ready for the flight now take us to
Africa all right so I I thought we were
going to hike out here
but hi I think in the morning hi in the
morning will be better we're going to
take the the thing up or yeah the car
all the way up and then no hiking up
there yeah there you going to walk up
there oh yeah so so we're ready yeah now
you're ready for it let's go all right
all right all right back yes sir Town
Table Mountain Wonders of the World this
is where we at guys come for [__]
throw up dude I got motion sickness let
go of any silver hand bars the floor you
are standing on will be
rotating I repeat step away from the
sides let go off any silver hand bars
and let's enjoy this lovely view we're
going full speed now it's too late to
turn around
I've never [__] hiked in my life
right here with some professional
hikers so see see that [__] very
professional so so what we're what 3500
ft in the air about yeah 1,700 M so he
was saying that you could actually hike
up this [__] yeah I've done it many
times dude you have to these people out
here a wild Florida we just walk places
we don't we don't hike Mountain this is
is probably a regular walk to the park
if in 30 minutes we don't catch the
[__] trolley down you know we have to
walk down right no we we just we just
hike down bro it's like 3
hours yeah like if if you think about it
if I run faster we can land right there
now what do you mean like over there no
no like on the other
side oh yeah
baby we got to take care of the people
[Music]
all right wait you're recording yeah all
right so I have something to
say this for you oh you [__]
this for you you
[__] this
[__] so he was actually looking
at the shoes like damn these are really
nice and I'm like you like them he's
like yeah I really like them I all right
thank
you oh let's go get
more about
$67,000 right now so if this trade hits
I'll successfully make about 150 to like
200,000 and that pays for what
nothing he already spent the $7,000 to
yeah that'll probably pay for probably
for like half the TR oh go they're going
to think I'm connected to the mafia all
around the world
it's funny how you've got to worry about
things like that when you're playing
like you're playing Jason all right so I
I did a little GI for you guys so I got
a little bit of some goods for you
guys come on baby that's what's up FX
Alex baby appreciate you Champion so
look so my card literally got declined
like five times it didn't let pass
100,000 Zar like it just just [__]
stop literally just stopped there so I
got three gifts for three guys and I got
more for the rest of the guys guys you
guys got gufts
[Music]
too I'm going literally show you guys
look so my car got declined look
literally look decline decline decline
decline decline [__] ver 70,000 Z so
I got you guys tomorrow with some [__] I
got much appreciate you br I'll be
waiting I'll be
waiting me I can't even go with
you appreciate you guys I'll see you
guys here tomorrow early yes sir we up
we ready got you how is it
[Applause]
[Laughter]
o bro you got to you got to treat the
people good look how half these people
go home now
so how's my trade though that's what
matters right now we got to make that
money back my trade right now is up
$8,000 oh never mind [__]
[Music]
$66,000 I think we actually taking the
longer Road you get to the back gate to
C the just Bey on that left goes to the
how many kilm 40 minutes
oh thank you so much Uncle see you thank
you Uncle so wait you say a left or a
right careful with the baboons
bro when just comes out the bush baboons
there literally was a big ass sign that
said be careful with the baboons water
break like I'm from
Florida shit's flat in Florida W
finally just Ste the whole way up
We Are the
Champion let's
go
anyway not right now oh
damn you sure that's him not a [__]
animal a that's
him you're a [__] Soldier here look
at this guy there's nothing this part of
me the extra weight I'm missing on my
legs with the whole cam gear and
everything man's a Savage bro I'mma hook
you up I'm going take it on the way
down who went the wrong
way T and them are
here where's the
waterfall so it's not
up oh [__] d d there's no [__] signal
in here [__]
we're going the wrong [__] way man
it's literally half day [__] this are so
bad think it's like 400 me in the wrong
way good news is [__] you came a long
way bad news is [__] you went the wrong
way there there's a sign there's a sign
right that
you right
[__] think I'd be the first to be like
leave me here just leave me today
my well you know what the camera guy
always survives yeah never so you good
course I'm going to stay close to this
guy right here dude it's literally say
it right there
waterfall Dam
[__] we're [__] blind is that
water I thought that was spelled wrong
for a second he literally said when you
go down 6
Kil 6K set and forget guys we got to
[__] set and forget let's just go right
you say left or right
technically the only way where we can go
left from here on us yeah but you sure
he say Left Right 100% we can get an
Uber if we
Marsh let's tou a
coin let's T the coin let's go he
definitely said left so okay you can
leave the way no okay let me go
I we lost we lost so long all right so
we just finished the hike and I'm like
yo I'm in a trade I completely forgot so
we're up right now $25,000 I take you
guys to the actual trade itself it's
creating very nice
lows currently Wi-Fi is not the best
here so all right so we just got back
from the hike the chefs have this ready
for us guys this is the definition of
life right now it's a Thursday morning
at 12:00 in the morning 6:00 a.m. man
time what are you doing on a Thursday at
12:00 probably at work which [__]
sucks sorry so you should start set and
forgetting not you're going to set and
forget this life right now all right
guys so I'm I'm from America I don't
know how to
drive but I don't have a license here I
don't know how to drive okay all right
so fun fact I'm a semi-professional
drifter in the US you guys know oh in
the US yeah like I'm actually like a
like a professional driver but in us
than God yeah but like on on that side
not on this side it's a little it's a
little confusing [__] something up oh
look oh yeah you blew the tire a
bro got one job [__] happens
right you did a nice job
[Applause]
yeah let me let me let me actually just
put these up for now just in case all
right so we just left the macro so it's
like a it's like a Walmart but in Africa
it's actually owned by Walmart so we
just spent right now
[Music]
84,000 Zar it's probably like almost
like $4,000 so we're going to get back
to 300 homes tomorrow in Cape Town so
coming back to the community you guys
got to do what you got to do want vodka
no no I'm good I'm
good all right so we're going to chug
the whole thing whoever whoever wins
just [__] wins go
no way he say
it D I'm
done who won who won I won yes
sir all right I'm going go your first
[__] off
now the craziest thing getting on this
side to I don't know it's just crazy to
me right now we're going to go uh do a
philanthropy play so we bought food
packages for every household for about
300 households shout out to Jason for
helping us out pretty much set
everything up and we're going to go now
into pretty much like the poorest
neighborhoods here in Cape Town and give
back to those neighborhoods quick trade
update trade is up now
$114,000 so we were up actually last
night
$45,000 Market just keeps fluctuating a
little bit kind of annoying but if I
decide to continue to hold I'll probably
close the trade about Tuesday of next
week so about 5 days for now so let's go
give back to these people in need and
let's hope we make it out good what do
you mean by that I don't know all right
guys so we're here in Cape Town so we're
here doing the philantropy play we're
pretty much getting every single
household little utility box with you
know food soap rice oil salt sugar all
these Necessities that you know some of
these sport nees out here don't have and
we're pretty much packing them all in
packages for every single household
we're going to hit 300 houses today we
have a long day today the boys have been
packing since 9:00 in the morning cuz
you know the store we got it from it to
buy everything individually pallets to
put it all together inside their own bag
so we can give out to the people and
everything is very organized the
logistics are done well so we're in that
process right now so let's see how it
goes we are a Youth Organization working
with the youth within our communities
through programs and various different
things to uplift them to upskill them
things like that welcome to R me is your
first time here okay welcome thanks for
offer you're going to make to us M did
you explain that you want to offer food
passes to
people um I'm just to go and call the
anti- the people yeah I'm come from
Dominican Republic it is a very poor
country and I know how it feels to to
struggle in life to get your family to
get better and I I know how it feels so
we come here from the other side of the
world yes we travel like 30 hours just
to to come here to come see you guys and
to give you guys some hope so we have
some food and some supplements for you
guys that we want to give you and I want
you to know that we love you and we want
to have you up
[Music]
[Applause]
there's a day before the meet and greet
here in South Africa hopefully the
weather is not like this tomorrow and we
thought Miami was bipolar F all right
guys so we're on our way right now to
The Venue uh we're pretty much going to
be doing the meet and greet with the
Traders here in South Africa and we told
people to pull up at 12:00 right and
it's currently it is actually right now
9:53 in the morning so it's 10:00 a.m.
people have been there since 7:00 in the
[__] morning morning which is insane
to us so we're going to go check them
out pretty much make sure everything's
going good and let's see how this
meeting G goes first time in South
Africa first time meeting South African
Traders which is a [__] ton of them it's
kind of cool we're on the way right
[Music]
now for
hey what's up guys we just got out of
the maid and greet we met like 500
Africans here a very nice people I'm
very glad with them do you have any
words to say
Alex a lot of questions and a lot of
questions were answered appreciate you
guys for coming out people came from all
around Africa glad to meet all of you
guys but now time to take a nap but you
know one thing this this was the first
meting grid that people really want to
learn yeah yeah yeah they were asking
too much questions yeah facts no no but
I think it's probably one of my favorite
ones we were really grateful for the
event look how far this [__]
goes holy [__] all right so we're making
on our way to the beach now
actually clean the lens right I
[Music]
see you going to get in I don't know is
there a
reward got
yeah is it
cold [__] want to get him almost
done you only need
like 100 more
[Music]
steps I just go home this feels
crazy
[__] life is like a
hike it sucks to climb up the
mountain when you get to the top is
worth
it and like in life I can hike in this
mountain I don't really know where I'm
going look you can see we're kind of
just Paving our way through this hike to
get up to the top it's going to be the
same thing with life you're going to
have to go through ways that you don't
know what you're doing but you figure it
out to get to the
top when you get to the
top it's all worth
it at least is the easy way
down I was saying some more
[__] sometimes in life you have to go
through ups and downs like kind of hik
in a
mountain and when you get to the top
it's all worth
it right
[Music]
I actually see a pengu I'm actually in
trip we drove an hour yeah we drove an
hour to
see there's no
way I I streak the Super Bowl think I
give a [__] about jumping this 2T W you
grab that
P there's another way we're finding
another way right
now
watch right there bro it's like the only
one
can't believe we're
leaving time to go this [__] so now
we're going to Dubai so but we're coming
back oh yeah we're coming back in
December yeah so we we're going to get
one of these houses probably for like 30
to 45 days in December we're going to
spend our winter here which is summer
here which is pretty cool but bro I love
this like I I have not look at that view
bro you don't get tired of this
and you don't get tired of this at all
so then we have a 10-hour flight to
Dubai and um after Dubai hopefully back
to Miami so is this for the weekend of
the life for the day in the life what's
this for pretty sure it's the whole week
it's probably the whole week
right all I can say is subscribe say
don't forget say don't forget baby
and S forgot